this is cool by the way the question location background
это классно кстати вопрос локация фон
cool you have hung up and we are from
классные вас есть повесил а мы из
kazakhstan to me of course yes but I have paris behind
казахстана мне конечно да но меня сзади
me on political topics I choose russia
я на политические темы я выбираю россии
on the topic of war and when talking I immediately
на тему войны и общаясь я сразу
identify everyone immediately understood
идентифицируешь все сразу понимали
where I could scold me I don’t swear myself
откуда я могла ругаете я сам не ругаюсь
there are people who  aggressively right away
есть люди которые агрессивно сразу
because, let’s not say, many do not
потому что не скажем многие не
perceive kuklin as an independent
воспринимают куклин как независимое
state, how do they say that there
государство как там говорят что не
are no Ukrainians as a nation, so
существует украинцев как нации так
now tell me please
дальше а теперь скажите мне пожалуйста
answer one question
ответьте на один вопрос
from Russia, in any case, you communicate with them,
с россии же в любом случае вы с ними
there are people who are positively
общаюсь есть люди которые положительные
loyal to Ukraine  yes, yes,
лояльно относятся украине есть да то
yes, but if you look like this, according to
есть но вот если смотреть так по
estimates, 1 out of 10 is no more than cotton wool out of
прикидкам 1 из 10 не больше вата из
ten, the sample that comes across in
десяти выборка вот которые попадаются в
chat roulette
чат-рулетке
one can be one that clearly
один может быть такой который четко
says that he does not support this,
говорит что он не поддерживает эту
took out normal weight, but yes, no, we have
вынула нормальный вес а так да нет у нас
adequate people  no one is supported by
адекватные люди никто не поддерживаются
me and I have that the number of these
я и я имею что количество этих
adequate springs is also
адекватных так вот пружинки тоже оно вот
small  oh, Belarusians, I watched it
такое небольшое белорусов я смотрел это
to their liking, everyone clearly speaks against the war
по душе все четко говорят против войны
against and now without any, but so the Russians,
против и ныне без всяких но так россияне
even if they, well, I don’t seem to
даже если им ну я вот вроде не
support them, but it’s your own fault they forced us there,
поддерживаем но вы сами виноваты там нас
and you watched the situation in
вынудили а вы наблюдали за ситуацию
Belarus that was two years ago and
беларуси которая была два года назад и
yes yes  Yes, I was then subscribed to the
да да да я тогда был подписан на
telegram channel inappropriately, that is,
телеграм-канал некстати по то есть я
when,
когда
well, let's say they went out very strongly, we
ну скажем они очень сильно выходили мы и
also watched the events in Kazakhstan,
за событиями в казахстане тоже смотрели
because we didn’t quite understand them,
потому что но мы их не совсем понимали
because everything was clear with Belarus,
потому что с беларуси у нас все понятно
so
так
it was with Kazakhstan, we  we don’t understand the
было с казахстаном мы не понимаем
local context, for example, the one
местный контекст так например тот кто
who went to the rallies, but with what
это выходил на митинги но с какими
specific requirements, that is, by
конкретно требования то есть
saying these events, this can be
сказав сие событиях этого получается
achieved and
достичь и
we still don’t understand that the mood
мы до сих пор не поняли что настроение
happened at the beginning of the year, but all
произошло в начале года но все
representatives of next, by the way, they are all
представители next а кстати они все
now more Polish, I’m again  why did they
сейчас польше я снова начала почему они
all move there, we look, we
все туда переехали туда мы смотрим
just observe in an interview, I just took
просто наблюдаем в интервью как раз брал
the index Russian from the creators of the
у создателей
new forces
новом сил выслан указательный русский
or not, I myself what kind of l  Caucasian
или нет я сам какое лицо кавказской
nationality doesn’t get hot there is a
национальности не нагреться есть
specific nationality I wouldn’t but
конкретно национальность я бы не стали а
there is a Dagestan there cuvee Kumyks there is an
дагестанец есть там cuvee кумыки есть
ayat about me Tabasaran I
аят об я табасаран
haven’t heard this but it’s a small
такого не слышал но это маленькая
thousand but I have a negative attitude towards me, by the
тысяч но я негативно отношусь у меня
way, I have Russian friends who
кстати друзья русские есть который в
live in Kazakhstan it’s
казахстане живут
very sad that they support this
очень печально что они поддерживают это
everyone and we are very friendly, but we
все и мы очень мы как бы дружим но мы
swear honestly, we sort things out
ругаемся честно скажу мы выясняем
, but at the same time I’m friends because I have
отношения но при этом дружу потому что у
my own position, I think that
меня своя позиция я считаю что
motivation can be
мотивация можно
tried by God, I’ll try this
попробуйте богу я попробую нафиг этот
dwarf in general, this is all started all the
карлик вообще вот это все затеял вот всю
garbage because now he is suffering  everything in the
фигню потому что сейчас страдает все в
post-Soviet space, everything in the CIS
постсоветское пространство все снг
suffers because of this, I hope you did
страдает из-за этого я надеюсь вы меня
n’t record me now, it’s not recorded, if
сейчас не записывали не записано если
you want, I won’t upload it, no, you
хотите не буду выкладывать нет вы меня
can upload
можете загрузить
me, I take this very negatively,
я отношусь к этому резко негативно
absolutely, I think that people have simply been
абсолютно я считаю что людям просто
brainwashed, I think that this is a
мозги промыли я считаю что это
crime against  people please
преступление против народа пожалуйста
my name
меня зовут
is a crime against the people against the
это преступление против народа против
people because ukraine  it’s the
людей потому что украина это
sovereign about the right to dispose of its
сувереном о вправе распоряжаться своим
sovereignty, so don’t you think that the
суверенитетом вот вам не кажется что тут
problem here is not only in the way there are a
проблема не только в пути нечто очень
lot of people in people in Russia they want the
много человек в людей в россии они хотят
revival of the Russian empire of the children
возрождение российской империи детского
narrowed it down, they don’t think of it as some kind of imperial
сузил это не мыслят какими-то имперскими
and let’s say this war in Ukraine is a
такими и скажем вот эта война в украине
seizure attack  I gave it
захватом нападение на грузию давала это
to Georgia in Chechnya, and
в чечне и так же
people also perceived it well, it’s
люди воспринимали это хорошо это
right, because Putin is
правильно потому что путин
restoring the territories, you know what
восстанавливает территории знаете вот
your name is Andrey Andrey when it
вас как зовут андрей андрей когда речь
comes to patriotism within the country,
заходит о патриотизме внутри страны
it
значит стране что-то не так происходит
means that something is wrong in the country, it means that something is wrong in the country
значит что то не то в стране творится
once and just try to
раз и просто пытаются от каких-то вещей
take their eyes off some things, just look now they
отвести глаза просто взгляд сейчас они
just wanted to leave at the expense of Ukraine in
хотели просто за счет украины выехать по
fact, well, it seems to me that I can be
факту ну мне так кажется я могу
wrong, it doesn’t work out in styles, they didn’t
ошибаться не получается стилях у них не
succeed there, we can infuriate me most of all
получилось там мы можем мне больше всего
these stickers
бесят эти наклейки
can show you sleep  Bering divisibility
можем показать вам сна беринга делимости
is such an annoyance to me because whether
такое меня это раздражает потому что ли
these times are already different there, you need
эти времена уже там различные нужно
to renew a new one  direction to move a
вновь новое направление двигаться
sane person I watch interviews of
здравомыслящий человек я смотрю интервью
people who are Russian who
людей которые русский который период
moved to turkey moved
переехали в турцию переехали в грецию
to greece because they say that
потому что они говорят что в соборность
there is no freedom of speech in russia now and they are
свободы слова в россии сейчас нет и они
moving in general my message is that all
переезжают в общем мой посыл такой все
this is [ __ ] sooner or later it will all
это фигня рано или поздно это все
end here [ __ ]  in the sense from
закончится вот фигня в смысле со стороны
Russia, people will see clearly, they will
россии люди прозреют однозначно они
see clearly, and then the whole world will
прозреют а украине весь мир потом будет
help ukraine to help recover and the
помогать помогать восстанавливаться и
status of ukraine in general in the global
статус украины вообще во всемирном
sense it will grow ukraine and in
отношении он вырастет украины а в
ukraine now a lot of people have learned about aukro and
украине сейчас много кто узнал о аукро и
no one knew with this let's start here all this
никто не знал с этого начнем вот вся эта
rex all  this action in quotation marks, the military
рекс все это действие в кавычках военная
operation played in the opposite
операция сыграл то в противоположную
direction, in fact, now, and Ukraine knows
сторону по факту сейчас а украине знает
all of Europe, America,
вся европа америка
children in the United States, there, in America itself, they know
дети в сша там в тоже сама мерике знают
what Ukraine
что такое украина
is, everything
вот все
entered the international arena, it came out much
на международную арену на вышла намного
stronger, came out before due to this everything and
сильнее вышла до за счет этого всего и
want and  the whole world will help
хочется и украины будет помогать весь
ukraine everything ukraine will come out
мир все украина выйдет
this is my position close
это моя позиция закройте
i will tell you  promised yes I’m closing
я вам пообещал да я закрываю
I just see you a good
я просто вижу вас камера хорошего
quality camera you can have
roulette папик если русскими по а вот
my channel  upholstery yes, I will subscribe to you
все вылез обивка да я на вас подпишусь а
, but
вот вот
yes, there is, but
да есть а
maybe just please close
может только пожалуйста закройте
changing some of the people they close to who
меняя часть людей закрывают до которые
they want, I will close without problems, I can very much
хотят я закрою без проблем я очень могу
tell you one thing andrey thank ukraine
одно сказать вам андрей слава украине
thank you please
спасибо пожалуйста
on Dagestan itself and a sound from us, naming
люди на сам дагестан и звук от нас некой
Dagestan, even clearly the opposition did not subside
дагестану даже четко оппозиция не спадал
new ones, but almost all of your comments,
новых но почти все свои комментарии че
what do you think about blowing Kutya Lyudin, and so
вы думаете про дул кутьей людин и так
we kick you have a beer up to from your gentlemen
нас кики у вас пивку до из ваших господа
and kevin socks, it’s going on there duki would be
и носки kevin творится там дуки бы
glories and
славов и
subscribe to  channel
подписывайтесь на канал
wider you mind the
шире ты виду
continents will be more of this x plan
материки будут больше этого х плане
show it mind and subscribe to
показывать его виду и подписывайтесь на
kilo bingo pc pet video i think still
килограмм бинго pc pet видео я думаю еще
n  asha on the right of the whites to them only for an
наша справа белых к их только за ушел
hour left in the world it was round crock after
часа на свете будала круглым крок за
crochet we pass thinking and glory to
кроком мы проезжаем думать и слава
ukraine
украине